Hello again!
You're listening to Mariah Radio,
and we've got another rousing
segment for your aural pleasure.
Help, Midnight Mentor!
Our first letter is coming to
you from Forever 21, Pretty Baby.
Kai, get a load of this.
Once again, I was late to my little
rendezvous because of that thing.
You know the one.
Exactly!
The one by the station!
The crossing that never
opens when you need it to!
It's just gonna be...
Whoa!
Tell me how you really feel, pretty baby!
Uh...
You serious?
So I guess we aren't the only stand
users at this school after all, huh?
Right.
Toshikazu Hazamada enrolled
as a junior in Group C.
Apparently,
he and his buddy had a
falling out over something
trivial right before
the spring term started.
Seems the friend dissed Hazemada's
favorite idol or anime or something.
Normally, that'd be nothing
to write home about,
but everything changed one
night when the friend he was
arguing with gouged out his own
eye with a mechanical pencil.
It's crazy, right?
I hear Hazemada's friend
said this in the hospital.
When I came to, I was staring at my eyeball
in my hand with the only eye I had left.
So you're saying this guy
ripped out his friend's
eye and he used some kind
of stand to do the job?
Well, that could be what happened here,
but there's no surefire way to find out.
Remember, the average person
isn't able to see a stand.
Yeah, I don't know.
This all sounds fishy to me.
What did you just say?
Chosuke,
I don't know who you think you are, but
you've got no right to say that to me.
I've got a real job now, you know.
Hang on, you're actually working now?
Of course I am.
I managed to land myself a sweet
little gig in finance. Finance, huh?
You sure that isn't code
for Lone Shark or something?
For now, let's just say I'm
working with some good people.
That's great, but did
you forget about this?
We've got work to do.
Wait up, Josuke!
Master Koichi!
You're seriously gonna go too?
Just let that jackass Josuke handle it!
I have to do this.
Something evil's taking over our town.
And if Morioh's in danger,
then my mom,
dad, sis, and pretty much everyone else
I care about are in danger as well.
I'm scared, but it has to be done.
Wow.
What a gutsy thing to say.
Then again, I would expect
nothing less from my hero.
But still.
You guys will have to excuse
me as I've got to get home now.
Stay out of trouble, Master Koichi!
It doesn't look like he's
hiding out in this room.
Honestly, it'd be kind of
creepy if he was in here.
Him coming back to school and
acting like nothing happened.
Especially after digging out
his friend's eye with a pencil.
Guys like that are psychos.
Hey, Josuke, what are you doing?
I'm just taking a quick look
through this guy's locker.
Keep an eye out, Koichi.
The least you could do is give
me some warning next time.
All right, he left his bag,
so he did come back to school.
Looks like he's in the
tennis club and a manga fan.
And he'd be right at
home in a hoarder's club.
I don't see how he could have hidden that
bow and arrow in here with all this shit,
huh?
The hell is this wooden thing?
A sand!
Wait, no.
Looks like it's just an ordinary object.
Why would this freak have one of those
wooden mannequins they sell in art stores?
That scared the crap out of me.
What? How?
I touched it, and the
thing turned into me.
Well, I guess that pretty much proves it.
Hazemata's a stand user.
That's just great.
Turning into me.
Quite the cheeky move, pal.
The manga, Perman. You know it?
It can speak!
And it sounds just like you, Josuke!
If you read Perman, you'd know.
There's a copy robot in it.
It's handy, don't you think?
I bet you wish that you had
one right about now. Huh?
Hey, Koichi, what's
this guy mumbling about?
Who is this Perman guy?
You're telling me you haven't read Perman?
How's that even possible?
Are you sure you're Japanese?
That's enough!
I'll be asking the questions around here!
He's got my arm! Yusuke, no!
However, I must give you a fair warning.
My robot is one that you
won't want to have around.
Once it copies you, you'll be making
all the same movements it does.
Which means, it's really not a puppet.
It's actually a puppet master!
Koichi, watch out!
Hm.
Keicho.
Just like that, another
one bites the dust.
Best part, I didn't touch him.
The honor of knocking him into Kingdom
Come goes to you, his dear friend.
It's underhanded shit like that
that really gets my blood boiling.
Making others do your dirty
work because you don't have
the balls to come out and
take care of things yourself.
Nothing makes me want to
kick someone's ass more!
That's just great.
It seems as though I'm outside
of your range and if you
can't get any closer to me
then neither can your stand!
In other words Josuke as
long as I make sure to
always keep a little distance
between the two of us.
You don't have a snowball's
chance in hell of defeating me!
So,
you know my stand's name is show-off and
possessing this doll has
given my stand physical form.
As a result it can now be
seen by any ordinary person!
Damn you Hazamada!
My objective is simple!
Pulverize Jotaro to
within an inch of his life
and make sure he never
returns to this town!
He's just a pathetic outsider snooping
around and getting in our business?
Although,
a little birdie told me that Jotaro's Star
Platinum can stop time
for a couple of seconds.
There's not a single stand user among
us who can get anywhere close to him.
Actually, the one stand that can do the
job is the one that just copied you!
I'm taking you out of the game, but I'll
be sure to give Jotaro your regards!
The sound of painful
squishing, it's so sublime.
But as long as you didn't sever the nerve,
you might have a chance at seeing again.
That is if luck decides to smile on you.
Given his injury, I think
he'll be out for a while.
Well, that was easy.
Hey, pick up my bag.
It's time to start our hunt for Jotaro.
You made it too easy.
Now, if I'm not mistaken,
Jotaro's hotel is...
It's the, uh...
The Mariah Grand Hotel!
Oh yeah, that's it.
Koichi! Koichi!
Josuke, what happened?
You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm doing okay.
And you're tougher than
anyone gives you credit for.
Even though you're all busted up,
you still managed to tag that
imposter with your stand.
What do you mean?
I was only able to do that because of you.
The moment you sent me flying,
you healed my broken bones
with Shining Diamond's power.
But,
uh, do you think you could heal the
injuries I got when I slammed into the door?
I don't want to be a bother,
but I'm in a lot of pain.
You bet.
you've reached the Mariah
grand hotel yeah hi how's it
going i need jotaro kujo He
should be staying in room 324.
One moment, please.
Hurry up!
We have to tell Mr.
Jotaro about that stand
before it's too late!
Thank you for waiting.
Unfortunately, the line
for room 324 is busy.
You can try calling again later.
It's busy?
What?! Of course!
He must be talking to the copy!
This is just great!
It got to him first!
You sure, Josuke?
Hey, you found proof that there's
another stand user at your school?
That I have.
I'll fill you in at Mariah Station.
Let's meet at the square in front.
You can get there in 15 minutes.
Understood.
See you in front of the station in 15.
Easy as pie.
Shit! No answer. This is bad.
He must have left, then.
Which means they probably baited
Jotaro to go and meet them somewhere.
Damn.
All we can do now is go after the copy.
What do we do?
I couldn't tell you two
apart to save my life.
Yeah.
Stealing my face is weird enough.
But what really freaks
me out are his fingers.
How often do you catch a glimpse of
your fingers compared to your face?
I realize that standard copied
me down to the finger press.
Huh?
Hey, Josuke.
You're back early.
Where's Master Koichi?
Hazamada, what the heck
are you doing here?
Tamami Kobayashi, huh?
You have no idea why we're hanging out?
Come on, give it a guess.
I'm all guessed out!
So you don't even have one little theory?
Should I have one, sir?
Nah, you're good.
Step on it.
If we don't hurry and catch up
with Hazamada, Jotaro is done for!
We can't let Jotaro meet up with the
copier, it'll be a total disaster!
Yeah, but I haven't figured out a solution
yet, so for now, all we can do is run!
We'll catch you later, Josuke.
See you tomorrow. Yeah, take it easy.
See you yet, Josuke.
Bye, Josuke.
Have a good evening.
Why the hell are these chattering
schoolgirls only saying goodbye to you?
No one ever says stuff like that to
me when I leave school for the day.
Why should I care since every
girl in this school is butt-ugly?
Josuke? Huh?
Um, could you read this?
Well, bye then!
Why are you accepting notes from
her, like it would do you any good?
Goddammit!
What the hell makes a jerk
like you so special anyway?
What's your deal?
The show's over now,
so let's just move on.
Maybe you've forgotten, but we
don't have time to dilly-dally.
How dare you speak to me that way!
That hurts!
Punching a guy made of wood
was bound to end badly.
That was pretty stupid of you.
Shut the hell up and cry crowding me!
Damn it.
He's really starting to get to me.
This always happens with my stand.
Like when I copied my
crush Junko the other day.
She morphed into a complete bitch.
I couldn't take it, so the
entire thing was a flop.
Is there no one halfway decent
on this miserable planet?
That damn Josuke'll get his.
But first I have to take care of Jotaro.
I'll crush him into paste.
This is gonna be good!
Huh?
You've got to be kidding that
guy smudged my motorcycle
What a douche damn that
dumbass and his dirty fingers.
I'm gonna kill him.
Take it easy man It was
probably an accident,
you know besides What do you think
I care if that asshole hears me?
Just look at how he's
walking damn It's like
watching a dying cricket
on a death march Oh, man!
That was a sick burn!
Good one, dude! Yeah? You think?
It was pretty funny.
That's it! Show off!
Hold him still while I settle the score.
What the hell are you doing, you freak?
Knock it off!
Now, don't worry your pretty little
head about what I'm gonna do.
Just focus on relaxing and I'll make
sure you never open that mouth again
A glass shard?
Josuke Higashikata?
What the hell?
Even the shrimp's still alive!
Hazamada!
Finally caught up to you and Pinocchio.
How soon we forget.
Come face to face with my
show-off if you dare, Josuke.
The moment you do, you'll
instantly be turned into a puppet.
Control him!
Now show off!
Not so fast.
What's happening?
You mean it isn't obvious?
That glass shard I chucked your
way wasn't meant to take you out.
I threw it so that it would
reform into its original shape.
You sliced off my right hand,
and it turned back into one.
This isn't good, Hazamada.
Settle down.
Just pretend you're resting
your hand in your pocket.
No one's gonna know.
More importantly, that bastard Jotaro
should arrive at the station any minute now.
As much as I'd like to get rid of Josuke,
we don't have time to
waste tracking him down.
Asamata!
Wait for me!
I see.
So they're meeting in
front of the station, huh?
We have to get moving!
Those two already have a head start!
Not to mention the fact
that the road they just
took is the fastest way
to get to the station!
Yeah, you're probably right.
But I've got a secret weapon
in tow, Koichi. You do?
so he's not here yet i guess he
ran into some trouble what's the
word you see josuke anywhere nope
nowhere to be found there's nothing
to worry about though if i so much
as glance at him he'll be turned
into my puppet in a flash huh hear
that Hazamada a train's coming
It's the crossing from hell!
Winning will cost valuable time,
so let's cut through the station!
Even if he catches up to us, the
train will stop him! Take that!
There's one minute left,
and all sights point to us making
it to the meeting spot first.
I win!
What the?
Look there!
It's Joesta and that brat Koichi!
Why's the crossing open?
Will someone explain
what the hell's going on?
Hazamada! Over there! Damn it!
He tricked us!
What is that stand?
Great, right?
You make the perfect secret weapon.
Thanks for the assist back there, Koichi.
There he is!
Hey, Jotaro! It's me!
It's Josuke! Huh? Hey.
We made it in time!
Boy, we got Hazamada
good, didn't we, Josuke?
Did something happen?
A copy?
A stand that copied your likeness
down to the fingerprints?
Yeah, it's crazy, right?
If he'd gotten to you before me and
Koichi, who knows what would have happened?
But at least, now we can relax a bit.
I severed its right hand, so it
ought to be easy to tell us apart.
I had to think on my feet, but
figured that would be best.
Now we play the waiting game.
Got it.
We weren't that far ahead, so
they should show up pretty soon.
Right.
Huh?
What am I doing with this?
This doesn't make sense.
Why would I take a pen
out of Jotaro's pocket?
I can't move.
It's like my arm is frozen in place.
Wait…
the other side of the
glass… Shit! It's him!
Jousuke Higashikata.
Like it or not, you're gonna plunge
that pen into Jotaro's brain.
The blunt force trauma
should kill him instantly.
After all, leaving him alive
isn't really an option now, is it?
Your stand would only heal him anyway.
It's your fault!
You're meddling as the
cause of this, Jousuke!
I was only gonna beat
Jotaro up and chase him out
of town before you involved
yourself in my business!
But now Jotaro's gonna die!
And it'll be by your hand!
Live with that, you uppity-asshat!
Do it!
Send him to hell!
Show off!
Jotaro!
Bastard!
Huh?
Is something the matter, Josuke?
Uh, no.
Though fortunately for me,
it looks like those biker dudes
finally tracked down Hazamada.
You're just where Josuke said
you'd be a piece of bug shit!
Hiding out at the station
like the coward you are!
That Josuke Fool is swell!
He went out of his way
to treat our wounds,
even if I don't totally
understand how we fixed them!
You know what time it is?
It's time we paid you back
for the stunt you pulled!
There's somethin' out behind the
bathroom and we're dyin' to show ya.
I'm not gonna lie, that stand can
be pretty scary if it copies you.
Alright, time to send it to
the big workshop in the sky.
I'll feel a lot better
once it's destroyed.
Meanwhile, Tamami was
admitted to the hospital.
What a self-destructive fool!
You have my condolences!
It's pain, it is old, I'm tired.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly!
To the arms and the lips and the face.
Of the human kind of all
that I need to, I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you!
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
But, ooh, I'm done by now.